resourcepack.net 2019-11-19

# Privacy Policy | Minecraft Resource Packs

ResourcePack.net may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 2018/06/15.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.

**Analytics Providers**

We may use third-party Web analytics, such as Google Analytics. These service providers use a variety of tracking technologies such as cookies to analyze how users use the resourcepack.net. For more information on how Google Analytics uses data from our websites and how you can control the information sent to Google, [click here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, please [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)[.](https://mixpanel.com/optout) Because these opt outs are cookie-based, please note that if you get a new computer or device, install or start using a new browser, or erase or alter your browser’s cookie file, you may need to opt out again.

**Ad Networks**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies

We use the following ad networks:

  * Google Adsense ([Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/privacy.html))

**Especially Google Adsense Privacy Policy**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
